Hi, Today I want to present my Greenfoot individual project.
Black the Jumper
This game is Jump&Fall indie game.
that we will play as a Black.
We have to reach a goal using a floating block.
This is game instruction.
then the game have 4 difficulty
that have Easy,Normal,Hard,EX-Mode
Today I will show the Easy mode.
This is the Easy mode.
press Space to jump.
press Shift to control Black to the right side(X-axis).
press Ctrl to control Black to the up side(Y-axis).
We can't control Black when Black is on the air.
Fall to the ground count as 1 death.
This is some power value (Y-axis) we can show in this game.
You can restart the map and stage by press the restart button.
When we reach the goal or time's up.
It will show score,death,time you play this stage.
Play and compete with friend.
Thank for watching.
Created by Kasidech Chumkun 59130500202.